http://www.premierdefense.net/privacy-policy.html

Back
Are You Falsely Accused?
Back
Are You Falsely Accused?
Privacy Policy
1. Collection of Data.Our registration process requires only a valid e-mail address and a unique user ID and password. Providing us with other information is at your option. Please take note that your user name, e-mail address, or other submissions that you make on this site may contain your real name or other personally identifiable information and, as a result, may appear on this site. Like many web sites, we may also automatically receive general information that is contained in our server log files such as your IP address and cookie information. Information about how advertising may be served on this site (if at all) is set forth below.
2. Use of Data.We may use Data to customize and improve your user experience on this site. We will make efforts so that your Data will not be provided to third parties unless (i) provided for otherwise in this Privacy Policy; (ii) we obtain your consent, such as when you choose to opt-in or opt-out to the sharing of Data; (iii) a service provided on our site requires the interaction with or is provided by a third party, by way of example an Application Service Provider; (iv) pursuant to legal process or law enforcement; (v) we find that your use of this site violates our this Policy, Terms of Service, other usage guidelines or as deemed reasonably necessary by us to protect our legal rights and/or property; (vi) or (vi) this site is purchased by a third party whereby that third party will be able to use the Data in the same manner as we can as set forth in this Policy. In the event you choose to use links that appear on our site to visit other web sites, you are advised to read the privacy policies that appear on those sites.
3. Cookies.Like many web sites, we set and use cookies to enhance your user experience, such as retaining your personal settings. Advertisements may appear on our web site and, if so, may set and access cookies on your computer and is subject to the privacy policy of those parties providing the advertisement. However, the companies serving the advertising do not have access to our cookies. These companies usually use non-personally identifiable or anonymous codes to obtain information about your visits to our site.
4. Children.We do not allow persons who are ages thirteen or younger to become members of this site. For more information, please contact our webmaster.
5. Editing or Deleting Your Account Information.We provide you with the ability to edit the information in your user account information that you provided to us in registration by using your personal page configuration area. You may request deletion of your user account by contacting our webmaster. Content or other data that you may have provided to us and that is not contained within your user account, such as posts that may appear within our forums, may continue to remain on our site at our discretion even though your user account is deleted. Please see our Terms of Use for more information.
6. Changes to this Privacy Policy.We may make changes to this Policy from time to time. We will notify you of substantial changes to this Policy either by posting a prominent announcement on our site and/or by sending a message to the e-mail address you have provided to us that is contained within your user settings.
7. No guarantees.While this Privacy Policy states our standards for maintenance of Data and we will make efforts to meet them, we are not in a position to guarantee these standards. There may be factors beyond our control that may result in disclosure of data. As a consequence, we disclaim any warranties or representations relating to maintenance or nondisclosure of Data.
8. Contact Information.If you have any questions about this Policy or our web site, please feel free to contact our webmaster
Practicing Areas in Ohio, Kentucky and Federal Courts
My criminal and dui-ovi defense practice covers all of Ohio, Kentucky, and Federal Courts in both states, including the following counties:
Adams County, Bath County, Bell County, Boone County, Bracken County, Brown County, Bourbon County, Butler County, Campbell County, Carroll County, Clermont County, Clinton County, Fayette County, Fleming County, Franklin County, Grant County, Gallatin County, Hamilton County, Harrison County, Henry County, Kenton County, Lewis County, Madison County, Mason County, Nicholas County, Owen County, Pendleton County, Robertson County, Rowan County, Shelby County, Scott County, and Warren County.
Criminal Defense and DUI Practice Includes the Following Cities In Ohio and Kentucky
Alexandria, Amelia, Arlington Heights, Batavia, Bellevue, Bethel, Blue Ash, Burlington, California, Carlisle, Cherry Grove, Cheviot, Cleves, Cincinnati, Colerain, Cold Spring, Crescent Springs, Crestview Hills, Covington, Dayton, Deer Park, Edgewood, Erlanger, Fairfield, Florence, Forest Park,  Franklin, Fort Mitchell, Ft. Thomas, Fort Wright, Green Township, Goshen, Hamilton, Harrison, Hebron, Hyde Park, Indian Hill, Independence, Kenwood, Lakeside Park, Lebanon, Lexington, Liberty Township, Loveland, Madeira, Mariemont, Mason, Melbourne, Middletown, Milford, Montgomery, Mount Healthy, Newport, New Richmond, Norwood, North College Hill, Oxford, Petersburg, Pierce Township, Reading, Richwood, Sharonville, Silver Grove, Silverton, Springboro, Springdale, St. Bernard, Trenton, Union, Union Township, Villa Hills, Walton, West Chester,  and Wyoming.
Call Today For a Free Consultation
FLORENCE
7310 Turfway Road
Suite 550
Florence, KY 41042
859-372-6670
Contact
CINCINNATI
Website Design and Development by Worldwide TeleNet Website Hosting by Worldwide TeleNet Worldwide TeleNet © 1995 - 2020
© 2009-2018 by Frank Mungo, Attorney At Law. All rights reserved.
